Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Toscanini recordings
  - Leonore - Overture No. 1 & Overture No. 2; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegretto; Symphony No. 8 in F Major, op. 93; String Quartet No. 16 in F Major, op. 135 - Beethoven, 11/25/1939; hupka_2524; MS 045519-1; Part 4 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 11.25.1939 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 1 & Overture No. 2; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegretto; Symphony No. 8 in F Major, op. 93; String Quartet No. 16 in F Major, op. 135 - Beethoven, 11/25/1939; hupka_2525; MS 045520-1; Part 5 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 11.25.1939 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 2 - Beethoven, 11/25/1939; hupka_2455; Part 6; MS-045521-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 2 - Beethoven, 11/25/1939; hupka_2526; MS 045521-1; Part 5 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 11.25.1939 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 2 - Beethoven, 11/25/1939; hupka_2527; MS 045521-1; Part 5 [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 11.25.1939 concert - It is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 2 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/25/1939; hupka_1463; Studio 8-H Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 2 - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/25/1939; hupka_1464; Studio 8-H Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 2 - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 11/25/1939; hupka_1465; Studio 8-H Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven; [Symphony No. 25 or 40] in G minor - Mozart, 4/26/1936; hupka_3132; Sides 6 & 8; WABC Station - 3:00pm; Farewell broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven; [Symphony No. 25 or 40] in G minor - Mozart, 4/26/1936; hupka_3133; Sides 5 & 7; WABC Station - 3:00pm; Farewell broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven, hupka_2485; # 021503-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven, hupka_2502; # 043428-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Part 3), hupka_2005; Record # D5-RC-487-1A; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1844; 043558-1; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 11/4/1939; hupka_1845; 043558-1; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 12/19/1944; hupka_2015; D4-RC-683-3; not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 11/4/1939; hupka_1846; 043559-1; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 12/19/1944; hupka_2016; D4-RC-684-3A; not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 11/4/1939; hupka_1847; 043560-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 11/4/1939; hupka_1848; 043561-1; Shellac disc
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 12/19/1944; hupka_2023; D4-RC-685-2; not released; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Leonore - Overture No. 3; Fidelio - Overture - Beethoven, 10/28/1939; 11/4/1939; hupka_0041; Leonore & Fidelio are the same opera, but different versions; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Leonore - Overtures No. 1, 2, 3; Fidelio - Overture - Beethoven, 10/28/1939; 11/4/1939; 11/25/1939; hupka_0042; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Leonore, op. 72 - Overture - Beethoven; Passacaglia & Fugue in C minor, BWV 582 - Bach; Civetta & friend in chapel, hupka_0322; Passacaglia - "Accordeons"; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Les Boeufs - Pierre Dupont, 3/1/1905; hupka_1220; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Contes d'Hoffmann - Les oiseaux dans la charmille - Offenbach, circa 1903-1908; hupka_0948; Serial # BFR-244-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Eolides - Franck, 3/5/1949; hupka_2650; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Eolides - Franck (Part 1), 5/22/1940; hupka_3467; Record # 050834-2R; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Les Eolides - Franck (Part 2), 5/22/1940; hupka_3479; Record # 050835-2R; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Les Hugenots - Bianca al par neve alpina - Meyerbeer, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0866; Serial # 329-A1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Hugenots - O beau pays de la touraine - Meyerbeer, [6/9/1911]; hupka_1187; Serial # 2222-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Huguenots - Bianca al par di neve alpina - Meyerbeer, 1/16/1928; hupka_1914; CVE-41449-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Huguenots - Bianca al par di neve alpina - Meyerbeer, 1/16/1928; hupka_1915; CVE-41449-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Huguenots - Piff! Paff! - Meyerbeer, 1/14/1910; hupka_1218; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Huguenots - The Page's Song (Nobil signori, salute!) - Meyerbeer, 2/11/1905; hupka_1209; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Huguenots - The Page's Song (Nobil signori, salute!) - Meyerbeer, 10/12/1906; hupka_1210; Shellac disc
  - Les pêcheurs de perles - Je Crois Entendre Encore - Bizet, 12/18/1929; hupka_4035; Written in Italian on item: Pescatore di Perle - Mi par d'udir ancora. Serial # 58119-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les pêcheurs de perles - Je Crois Entendre Encore - Bizet, 12/18/1929; hupka_4036; Written in Italian on item: Pescatore di Perle - Mi par d'udir ancora. Serial # 58119-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Pecheurs de Perles (Pearl Fishers) - Non hai compreso - Bizet, hupka_1025; Serial # IRCC-64-B;; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les Rameaux - Fauré, 1/24/1905; hupka_0804; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Les saisons - Air du laboureur - Haydn, 2/20/1905; hupka_0806; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Li marinari - Rossini, 4/4/1911; hupka_1899; 87078; Shellac disc
  - Lieder, op. 17 - Ständchen (Serenade) - R. Strauss, [04/02/1923]; hupka_3980; B-27731; Shellac disc
  - Light Cavalry [Leichte Kavallerie] - Overture - Franz von Suppé (Pt. 1), hupka_3604; D5-RC-16-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Light Cavalry [Leichte Kavallerie] - Overture - Franz von Suppé (Pt. 2), hupka_3605; D5-RC-17-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lili - Guetary [?], 5/17/1903; hupka_1082; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Linda di Chamounix - O luce di quest 'anima - Donizetti, hupka_3774; IRCC-92-A; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Linda di Chamounix - O luce di quest' anima - Donizetti, [11/02/1908; hupka_4052; Serial # 88142; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Little Mary - ?, 1906; hupka_3530; 2121-E; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Little Mary - ?, 1906; hupka_3542; 2121-E; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lobetauz, An allen Zweigen - Ludwig Thuille, Mar. 1912 [03/14/1912]; hupka_3978; Serial # C-11528; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lodoletta - Ah! Ritrovarla nella sua capanna - Pietro Mascagni, hupka_4034; Serial # 74615; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Act III, Love Duet - Wagner (Pt. 1), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3872; 7150-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Act III, Love Duet - Wagner (Pt. 2), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3873; 7150-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Cessâaro I canti alfin! - Wagner, 1908; hupka_1022; Serial # 8056-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Cigno gentie - Wagner, circa 1903-1908; hupka_1264; Serial # HRS-1025-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Dank, König, dir - Wagner, circa 1906-1909; hupka_3814; Serial # 92062; Shellac disc
  - Lohengrin - Das suisse lied verhallt - Wagner, hupka_0978; Serial # 542-I; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Das suisse lied verhallt - Wagner, hupka_0979; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Du Aermste - Wagner, [05/25/1908]; hupka_1010; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Einsam in trüben Tagen - Wagner, hupka_0976; Serial # 538-I; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Einsam in trüben Tagen - Wagner, hupka_0977; Serial # 538-I; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Einsam in trüben Tagen - Wagner, [03/05/1904]; hupka_3981; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Elsa's Dream - Wagner, [05/7/1904]; hupka_1890; 74014; Shellac disc
  - Lohengrin - Höchstes Vertrau'n - Wagner, circa 1909-1912; hupka_3118; Serial # 10822-U; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - In fernem dand - Wagner, 1/18/1906; hupka_3813; Serial # 74034; Shellac disc
  - Lohengrin - Merce, cigno gentil (Swan Song) - Wagner, 1908; hupka_1021; Serial # 88603; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - mio salvatore - Wagner, 1908; hupka_1023; Serial # IRCC-104-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lohengrin - Prelude to Act I - Wagner, 2/24/1941; hupka_3407; Remakes of this recording were done on 03/17/1941 & 05/06/1941; Record # 062532-3A; Shellac disc
  - Lohengrin - Prelude to Act I - Wagner, 2/24/1941; hupka_3419; Record # 062533-4; Shellac disc
  - Lohengrin - Prelude to Act I - Wagner (Part 2), 5/6/1941; hupka_3431; Record # 062533-4A;remake of session from 02/24/1941; Shellac disc
  - Lohengrin - Prelude to Act I - Wagner (Part 2), 5/6/1941; hupka_3443; Record # 062533-4; Shellac disc
  - Lolita (Spanish Serenade) - Arturo Buzzi-Peccia, 10/22/1907; hupka_1148; Shellac disc
  - Loreley - Ah, dunque ei m'amera - Alfredo Catalani, 4/4/1910; hupka_1155; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Alfredo Catalani, 3/21/1947; hupka_2881; Studio 8-H - Pt. 2; Rehearsal; "Toscanini throws baton on the floor, the music stand down the steps, his watch in the audience room - then walks out; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani, 3/21/1947; hupka_3098; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 4; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani, 3/21/1947; hupka_3099; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 4; Shellac disc
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani, 3/21/1947; hupka_3101; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Disc 2; CD on EC; Shellac disc
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani, 3/21/1947; hupka_3204; Rehearsal; QC-1615-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani, 3/21/1947; hupka_3223; Rehearsal; Disc #4; B-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani, 3/22/1947; hupka_2867; Rehearsal; Sides 1 & 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani; La Wally - Prelude to Act IV - Catalani, 3/22/1947; hupka_2866; Rehearsal; Sides 2 & 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Dance of the Nymphs - Alfredo Catalani; La Wally - Prelude to Act IV - Catalani; Fountains of Rome - Respighi, 3/22/1947; hupka_2865; Rehearsal; Sides 2 & 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Loreley - Lascia per ceh libera - Alfredo Catalani, 1917; hupka_1340; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lorenzo Fuller Show, 6/5/1951; hupka_2368; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Los ojos negros - F. M. Alvarez, [7/26/1906]; hupka_2003; C-3628; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Louisa Miller - Quando le sere al placido - Verdi, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3874; 6843-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Louise - Depuis le jour - Gustave Charpentier, 10/3/1913; hupka_0954; Serial # A 13900; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Ardon gli incensi; splendon le sacre faci (Mad Scene, Pt. 1) - Gaetano Donizetti, 1908; hupka_4007; Serial # 1453 1/2-C; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Cruda funesta smania - Donizetti, hupka_3433; 5191-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Cruda funesta smania - Donizetti, 5/27/1912; hupka_3453; 220-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Dalle stanze - Donizetti, 9/11/1923; hupka_3890; CE-1279-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Dalle stanze ove Lucia - Donizetti, 1/26/1916; hupka_3664; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Dolce suono (Mad Scene) - Donizetti, hupka_0953; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Mad Scene - Donizetti, circa 1903-1915; hupka_3842; 2500; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Quando rapita in estasi - Donizetti, circa 1903-1915; hupka_3841; 3078-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Reguava nel silenzio - Donizetti, circa 1903-1915; hupka_3840; 3077-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Spargi d'amaro pianto - Gaetano Donizetti, hupka_4008; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucia di Lammermoor - Tu che a Dio spiegasti l'ali - Donizetti, [03/23]/1910; hupka_1267; Serial # A-8740; Shellac disc
  - Lucrezia Borgia - Brindisi - Donizetti, hupka_1966; 3487-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucrezia Borgia - Di pescatore ignobile - Donizetti, [10/18]/1907; hupka_1149; HRS-1003-A; Shellac disc
  - Lucrezia Borgia - Di pescatore ignobile - Donizetti, hupka_1238; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucrezia Borgia - Drinking Song / It Is Better to Laugh than be Sighing - Donizetti, 1/3/1906; hupka_4086; Serial # 85096; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lucrezia Borgia - Vieni, la mia vendetta - Donizetti, [05/05/1924]; hupka_1241; [74890] [Not released]; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Lullaby - Rachmaninoff, hupka_2159; 072131-1; Shellac disc
  - Luna d'estate - Paolo Tosti [lyricist - Riccardo Mazzola], [2/5]/1916; hupka_2421; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Luna Fedel - Luigi Denza, Nov. 1902; hupka_2031; Serial # 2882; "Very valuable; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Luna Fedel - Luigi Denza, Nov. 1902; hupka_2409; "Very valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Luna Lù - ? Ricciardi, circa 1903-1908; hupka_1276; Serial # 13340-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Ma Lisette, Au printemps - Gounod, [03/06/1908; hupka_1972; Shellac disc
  - Macbeth - Ah, la peterna mano - Verdi, 2/23/1916; hupka_3697; A-17197; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Macbeth - Pieta, rispetto - Verdi, hupka_3454; 052369; 234-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Macushla - Dermot MacMurrough, lyricist - Josephine V. Rowe, 3/30/1911; hupka_1655; 759-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madam Butterfly - Duet (Act I) - Puccini, hupka_1353; March 8 [no year]. Master No. 8011-A; Shellac disc
  - Madame Butterfly - Amore o grillo - Puccini, 1910; hupka_3117; HRS-2006-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Amore o grillo - Puccini, 3/14/1910; hupka_3698; 8014-B; A-8711; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Amore o grillo - Puccini, 3/14/1910; hupka_3701; 8014-B; Shellac disc
  - Madame Butterfly - Death Scene - Puccini, hupka_3884; 91086; 939-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Entrance of Cio-Cio-San - Puccini, [02/19/1907]; hupka_3956; B-4255-1; 87004; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Love Duet, Bimba.. [ILLEGIBLE] - Puccini (Pt. 1), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3875; 6832-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Love Duet, Io t'ho ghermita - Puccini (Pt. 2), circa 1930-1939; hupka_3876; 6832-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Ora A Noi - Puccini, 2/3/1908; hupka_4062; Serial # 89014; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Sai cos'ebbe cuore - Puccini, hupka_3870; 91084; 12654-U; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Tutti I fiori - Puccini, 10/2/1909; hupka_3951; Shellac disc
  - Madame Butterfly - Un bel di Vedremo - Puccini, 1908; hupka_0980; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madame Butterfly - Ve lo dissi - Puccini, 3/14/1910; hupka_3673; A-8712; 8014-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Mademoiselle de Belle Isle Si io t'amo - Spiro Samaras, circa 1908-1910; hupka_2556; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Madrigale - ? Floridia, 10/7/1910; hupka_3805; Serial # 74233; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Magdalen at Michael's Gate - Liza Lehmann, 10/2/1913; hupka_0955; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Maggio (Vocal Waltz), hupka_4009; Spelled "Galvani" on item; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Magic Flute - Aria della Regina - Mozart, [2/1]/1907; hupka_1164; Shellac disc
  - The Magic Flute - Grand Isi! Grand Osiri - Mozart [Zauberflöte, K. 620 - O Isis und Osiris], 1/24/1905; hupka_4124; Serial # 6371-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Magic Flute - Overture - Mozart, hupka_3119; Rehearsal; Disc 2; Shellac disc
  - The Magic Flute - Overture - Mozart, hupka_3120; Rehearsal; Disc 2; Shellac disc
  - The Magic Flute - Overture - Mozart, hupka_3159; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Tests; Disc 2; Shellac disc
  - The Magic Flute - Overture - Mozart, hupka_3160; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Tests; Disc 1; Shellac disc
  - The Magic Flute [Zauberflöte, K. 620] - Qui sdegno non s'accende - Mozart, [02/25/1905]; hupka_0803; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Magic Flute, K. 620 - Mozart, 11/6/1946; hupka_3215; 2-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Magic Flute, K. 620 - Mozart, 11/6/1946; hupka_3216; 1-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Malgré-moi - G. Pfeiffer, [4/01/1907]; hupka_3834; A 4362; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Malia - Paolo Tosti, hupka_3457; 2807-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Malia - Paolo Tosti, hupka_3458; 2807-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Mamma dice - Antônio Carlos Gomes, 5/11/1908; hupka_1894; 74125; Shellac disc
  - Mamma mia, che vo' sapè - Emanuele Nutile, 11/6/1909; hupka_3661; 6009-A; Shellac disc
  - Manfred Overture, op. 115 - Schumann (conc.), hupka_3177; D6-RC-6452-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Overture, op. 115 - Schumann (conc.), hupka_3189; D6-RC-6452-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Overture, op. 115 - Schumann (Pt. 1), hupka_3129; D6-RC-6450-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Overture, op. 115 - Schumann (Pt. 1), hupka_3141; D6-RC-6450-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Overture, op. 115 - Schumann (Pt. 2), hupka_3153; D6-RC-6451-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Overture, op. 115 - Schumann (Pt. 2), hupka_3165; Label / station: Victor - HMV; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (conc.), 11/10/1946; hupka_3499; D7-RC-7836-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3493; D7-RC-7833-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3500; D7-RC-7833; Label has been destroyed - info. taken from sleeve; Shellac disc
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 2), 11/10/1946; hupka_3494; D7-RC-7834-1 Broadcast; Shellac disc
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 2), 11/10/1946; hupka_3495; D7-RC-7834-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 3), 11/10/1946; hupka_3496; D7-RC-7835-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 3), 11/10/1946; hupka_3497; D7-RC-7835-2; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 3), 11/10/1946; hupka_3498; D7-RC-7835-2A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. I - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 4 - conc.), 11/10/1946; hupka_3519; D7-RC-7836-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. II - Tchaikovsky (conc.), 11/10/1946; hupka_3522; D7-RC-7838-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. II - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3520; D7-RC-7837-1A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. II - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3521; D7-RC-7837-1A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. II - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 2), 11/10/1946; hupka_3489; D7-RC-7838-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. III - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3490; D7-RC-7839-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. III - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3507; D7-RC-7839-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. III - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 2), 11/10/1946; hupka_3508; D7-RC-7840-1A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. III - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 3), 11/10/1946; hupka_3509; D7-RC-7841-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. III - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 3), 11/10/1946; hupka_3510; D7-RC-7841-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. IV - Tchaikovsky (conc.), 11/10/1946; hupka_3514; D7-RC-7844-1A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. IV - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 1), 11/10/1946; hupka_3511; D7-RC-7842-1A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. IV - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 2), 11/10/1946; hupka_3512; D7-RC-7843-1; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manfred Symphony in B minor, op. 50 - Mvt. IV - Tchaikovsky (Pt. 2), 11/10/1946; hupka_3513; D7-RC-7843-1A; Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Ah fuyez - Massenet, circa 1937-1949; hupka_1937; 2SB-2536-1; Shellac disc
  - Manon - Ah! Fuyez - Massenet, 12/27/1911; hupka_3662; 6020-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Duet (Act II) - Massenet, 12/30/1912; hupka_1352; Master No. 8011-B; Shellac disc
  - Manon - Flich', o flich'! - Massenet, circa 1909-1912; hupka_3130; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Gavotte [Obéissons quand leur voix appelle] - Massenet, 11/4/1912; hupka_1740; Serial # B-12563; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Helas, l'oiseau qui fuit - Massenet, hupka_1508; Serial # 10848-L; Cat # IRCC-80-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Il segno (En fermant les yeux) - Massenet, circa 1903-1908; hupka_0960; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Il segno (En fermant les yeux) - Massenet, circa 1903-1908; hupka_0972; Serial # 87049; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Il sogno - Massenet, [01/03]/1913; hupka_1777; A-12764; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - Il Sogno: Chiudo gli occhi - Massenet, Mar. 1902; hupka_2397; Serial # 1785-B; Cat # 52345; "Very valuable; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon - On l'appelle Manon - Massenet, 12/30/1912; hupka_3665; 8011-B; Shellac disc
  - Manon - The Dream - Massenet, 1909; hupka_3913; 1981-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon Lescaut - Ah! Non vavvicinate - Puccini, hupka_3712; OW-2539-2; DA 1385; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon Lescaut - Guardate, passo son - Puccini, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3877; 6843-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon Lescaut - In quelle trine morbide - Puccini, hupka_0910; IRCC-63-A; 2144-L; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon Lescaut - In quelle trine morbide - Puccini, 4/4/1912; hupka_1912; Serial # HRS-1014-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon Lescaut - O tentatrice! - Puccini, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3880; 7157-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Manon Lescaut - Tu! Tu! Amor - Puccini, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3878; 7157-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Maria di Rudenz - Ah, non avea piu lacrime - Donizetti, May. 1921; hupka_3459; CM-27-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Marien-Waltzer, op. 143 - Joseph Lanner, hupka_3273; BLR-5945-ITA; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Maritana - There is a flower - William Vincent Wallace, 12/11/1912; hupka_2971; A-12710; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Marriage of Figaro - Mozart (conc.), 3/15/1947; hupka_2805; Side 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Marriage of Jeannette - Nightengale Song - Victor Massé, 3/19/1909; hupka_1131; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Martha - Il mio lyonel - Friedrich von Flotow, hupka_3460; 052143; 883-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Martha - M'appari - Friedrich von Flotow, 2/11/1906; hupka_3666; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Martha - M'appari - Friedrich von Flotow, hupka_3590; 13200-R; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Martha - M'apparì - Friedrich von Flotow, 4/22/1908; hupka_1053; Serial # C-6137; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Martha - Povers Lionello - Friedrich von Flotow, 1907; hupka_3461; 92005; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Masked Ball [Un ball in maschera] - Barcole - Verdi, circa 1937-1940s; hupka_1374; Serial # OSB-2404-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Masked Ball [Un ball in maschera] - Barcole - Verdi, circa 1937-1940s; hupka_1386; Serial # OSB-2404-2; Lacquer discs/acetates